wallpaper4me.com 2015-05-30

# Wallpaper4Me.com | HD Wallpapers, High Definition Wallpapers, Twitter Backgrounds, Free Wallpapers, Myspace Backgrounds, Desktop Wallpapers, Desktop Backgrounds, Backgrounds For Myspace & More!

## Privacy Policy

**About Wallpaper4Me.com**

  * Wallpaper4Me.com is an online service that provides users with wallpapers to decorate their desktop background.

**Information Collection and Use by Wallpaper4Me.com**

  * Wallpaper4Me.com logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, demographic data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes.

**Links**

  * Wallpaper4Me.com contains links to sites. Wallpaper4Me.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on Wallpaper4Me.com.

**Google Advertisements**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on Wallpaper4Me.com.   
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to Wallpaper4Me.com and other sites on the Internet.   
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).  

**Other Third Party Advertising**

  * We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
